<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="repository.mrgee.kodi" name="MrGee Kodi Repository" version="1.0.0" provider-name="MrGee">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="MrGee Kodi Repository">
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">MrGee Kodi Repository</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Repository for MrGee Kodi addons.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.artwork.curator" name="Artwork Curator" version="0.30.18" provider-name="rmrector + Artwork Curator custom fork">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.20.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
        <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.8" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <menu id="kodi.core.manage">
                <item library="context.py">
                    <label>AC: add missing artwork</label>
                    <visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.curator) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode)]</visible>
                </item>
                <item library="context_gui.py">
                    <label>AC: select artwork</label>
                    <visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.curator) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode)]</visible>
                </item>
                <item library="context_debug_remove.py">
                    <label>AC: remove artwork references</label>
                    <visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.curator.debug) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode)]</visible>
                </item>
                <item library="context_debug_logitem.py">
                    <label>AC: log item debug info</label>
                    <visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.curator.debug) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode)]</visible>
                </item>
            </menu>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" start="login" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Remote-only artwork curator for Kodi video libraries.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Artwork Curator manages remote artwork for movies, movie sets, TV shows, seasons, and episodes. Artwork stays remote and is cached only in Kodi's internal texture cache. Indonesian content prioritizes Indonesian artwork before English and no-language fallbacks.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Remote artwork sources: The Movie Database, fanart.tv, and TheTVDB.</disclaimer>
        <news>v0.30.18 Artwork Curator runtime-debug beta
- Add continuous runtime debug logs for every menu command, service signal, provider request, cache operation, item phase, selection decision, and performance timing.
- Export diagnostics now includes runtime-debug.log, runtime-performance.csv, runtime-items.log, runtime-selection.log, runtime-provider.log, runtime-cache.log, runtime-errors.log, runtime-menu.log, and runtime-service.log.
- Provider request logs redact API keys and sensitive parameters.
- Logs rotate automatically when they grow too large.

v0.30.17 Artwork Curator diagnostics beta
- Add Export diagnostics to the main menu.
- Export Kodi logs, filtered Artwork Curator log lines, redacted settings, latest reports, Indonesian refresh log, processed-items state, and Indonesian movie artwork snapshot.
- Create a ZIP under userdata/addon_data/script.artwork.curator/ for easy upload and analysis.
- Keep API keys redacted in the settings snapshot.

v0.30.16 Artwork Curator movie-only-Indonesian beta
- Limit Indonesian-language specialization to movies inside Indonesian Movies collection folders.
- Remove Indonesian-specific handling for movie sets, TV shows, seasons, and episodes.
- Add explicit details fallback chain: configured/Kodi language, then en-US, then raw details.
- Keep provider/API index order for /images extras and fallback artwork.
- Rename the manual command to Refresh Indonesian movie artwork.

v0.30.15 Artwork Curator provider-index-order beta
- Remove rating-based filtering and sorting from automatic artwork selection.
- Keep ratings and likes only as diagnostic information in logs.
- Select artwork deterministically by language priority, provider priority, provider/API index order, and minimum resolution.
- Remove the visible minimum-rating slider because it no longer affects selection.
- Keep localized Indonesian primary-poster handling and TPDb preservation.

v0.30.14 Artwork Curator rating-tier-fix beta
- Make all explicitly rated non-poster artwork rank above Not rated artwork.
- Treat the minimum-rating setting as a preferred tier instead of a hard rejection threshold.
- Sort non-poster artwork as: high-rated, low-rated, then unrated fallback.
- Keep poster selection independent from vote ratings.

v0.30.13 Artwork Curator unrated-fallback beta
- Treat unrated TMDb, fanart.tv, and TheTVDB artwork as fallback-only candidates instead of assigning a neutral rating of 5.
- Prefer rated non-poster artwork that meets the configured threshold.
- Allow unrated candidates only when no viable rated candidate remains.
- For multi-fanart slots, fill rated candidates first and use unrated rows only for remaining gaps.
- Keep poster selection independent from vote ratings.

v0.30.12 Artwork Curator poster-selection-fix beta
- Stop applying minimum vote-rating filtering to posters.
- Select posters by localized language priority, localized-primary promotion, TMDb gallery order, and minimum height.
- Keep minimum rating filtering for non-poster artwork.
- Fix cases where an unrated lower-priority poster incorrectly beat the localized TMDb primary poster.

v0.30.11 Artwork Curator dialog-fix beta
- Fix Refresh Indonesian artwork confirmation dialog labels.
- Move the TPDb preservation note into the message body.
- Use short Refresh and Cancel button labels.

v0.30.10 Artwork Curator debug-log-fix beta
- Fix Indonesian refresh debug logging on Kodi portable profiles.
- Replace unsupported xbmcvfs append mode with translated local-path append writes.
- Keep the full Indonesian poster diagnostic output unchanged.

v0.30.9 Artwork Curator Indonesian-debug beta
- Add a dedicated Indonesian refresh debug log viewer.
- Log scan inclusion, TMDb IDs, current poster URLs, candidate posters, sizes, ratings, localized-primary flags, selected URL, update URL, and JSON-RPC verification.
- Recognize Indonesian Movies (Collection) folder names in addition to [Collection] and plain variants.
- Keep the localized-poster flow unchanged while gathering actionable diagnostics.

v0.30.8 Artwork Curator beta
- For Indonesian media, promote localized TMDb details.poster_path from language=id-ID as the main poster.
- Reuse /images metadata for the promoted poster so minimum-height filtering still applies.
- Keep /images gallery order for fallbacks and retain extra-artwork provider logic.
- Preserve TPDb and other manual non-curator URLs during Indonesian refresh.

v0.30.7 Artwork Curator beta
- Follow TMDb poster-gallery order within the selected language and provider.
- Stop forcing details-endpoint poster_path ahead of TMDb gallery candidates.
- Use poster_path only as a fallback when TMDb /images has no poster rows.
- Retain minimum poster-height filtering and Indonesian language priority.

v0.30.6 Artwork Curator beta
- Enable automatic processing for new library items once after upgrade.
- Add clear log messages when automatic processing is queued.
- Write and read the latest-run report through xbmcvfs for better Kodi profile compatibility.
- Add a configurable minimum poster height and default it to 1000px.
- Prevent TMDb details-endpoint primary posters from bypassing poster quality filtering.

v0.30.5 Artwork Curator report-fix beta
- Always write a dedicated latest-run summary when processing finishes.
- Make final notification totals and visible report totals use the same completed-run data.
- Show artwork counts grouped by type and scanned items grouped by media type.
- Keep the rolling history report below the latest summary.

v0.30.4 Artwork Curator beta
- Add a new manual menu action: Refresh Indonesian artwork.
- Re-check Indonesian movies, TV shows, episodes, and the Indonesian Movies Collection using language priority id -> en -> no language.
- Preserve existing TPDb and other manually chosen non-curator remote URLs while refreshing curator-managed artwork.
- Keep TV-show season artwork in sync during Indonesian refresh.

v0.30.3 Artwork Curator stability beta
- Prevent screensaver and idle shutdown while artwork scans, cache warming, and pruning are running.
- Recover from malformed individual library items and provider-response errors without stopping the full scan.
- Write recovered Python tracebacks clearly to kodi.log.
- Add top-level service exception recovery.

v0.30.2 Artwork Curator beta
- Automatically migrate legacy profile data after the add-on ID rename.
- Import old artwork reports, processed-item state, and missing settings such as API keys.
- Rename the internal Home-window busy property to ArtworkCurator.Status.
- Show a clear message when no report exists yet.

v0.30.0 Artwork Curator beta
- Renamed the visible add-on from Artwork Beef Video Remote to Artwork Curator.
- Added a new Artwork Curator icon.
- Simplified settings into General, Artwork, Providers, and Advanced.
- Standard movie, set, TV-show, season, and episode artwork remains enabled automatically.
- Internal add-on ID changed to script.artwork.curator. Uninstall the older custom build with the old ID to avoid duplicate services.

v0.29.8 custom fast beta
- Episode artwork is simplified to thumb and landscape only.
- Legacy episode fanart and fanart# references are removed during the next normal episode scan.
- Movie, set, TV-show, and season fanart behavior is unchanged.

v0.29.7 custom fast beta
- Bulk artwork scans now assign remote URLs without downloading texture-cache files by default.
- Use Cache missing remote artwork separately after the scan when desired.
- Batch texture-cache downloads now use a bounded four-worker pool.
- Texture index is reused for the whole run and the artificial per-item delay is reduced.

v0.29.6 custom beta
- Compact progress actions are now English, title case, and exactly one word: Checking, Reading, Searching, Selecting, Adding, Downloading, Removing, Cleaning, Skipping, Missing, and Done.
- Artwork type remains visible when relevant, for example: Artwork Curator: Downloading · fanart3.

v0.29.4 custom beta
- Detailed compact progress stages: checking slots, remote search, library updates, and texture-cache downloads.
- Progress headings include artwork types such as poster, fanart3, clearlogo, and landscape.

v0.29.3 custom beta
- Restore compact persistent Kodi background progress notification.

v0.29.2 custom beta
- Manual artwork scans now use the original compact persistent Kodi background progress notification.
- Cache-missing, prune-cache, and force-recache actions use the same visible background progress style.

v0.29.1 custom beta
- Removed music, music-video, artist, album, and song workflows.
- Remote-only artwork references. No media-folder artwork downloads or extrafanart folders.
- Added TMDb TV-show and season artwork provider.
- Indonesian artwork priority and raster-only filter.
- Added missing-cache, prune-cache, and force-recache menu actions.
- Preserve manually selected extensionless remote artwork URLs, including TPDb-style asset URLs.</news>
        <source>https://github.com/rmrector/script.artwork.curator</source>
        <website>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.curator/</website>
        <license>The MIT License</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets><icon>icon.png</icon></assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.library.ratings.scraper"
       name="Library Ratings Scraper"
       version="1.5.0"
       provider-name="OpenAI">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="context.py">
                <label>Refresh ratings data for selected item</label>
                <visible>String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,episode) | !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.DBID)</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Scrape, cache and publish library ratings, statuses and IMDb Top 250 rank</summary>
        <summary lang="id_ID">Scrape, cache and publish library ratings, statuses and IMDb Top 250 rank</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Scans selected Kodi media types, stores ratings/statuses/awards/IMDb Top 250 rank in an independent cache, and publishes TMDbHelper-compatible window properties for Arctic Fuse 3. Version 1.5.0 is the stable cleanup release: diagnostics redact API keys, reports are clearer, RT badge diagnostics are safer, bundled IMDb Top 250 remains the source, and default debug/auto-scrape settings stay off.</description>
        <description lang="id_ID">Scans selected Kodi media types, stores ratings/statuses/awards/IMDb Top 250 rank in an independent cache, and publishes TMDbHelper-compatible window properties for Arctic Fuse 3. Version 1.5.0 is the stable cleanup release: diagnostics redact API keys, reports are clearer, RT badge diagnostics are safer, bundled IMDb Top 250 remains the source, and default debug/auto-scrape settings stay off.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>