<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.program.steam.library" name="Steam Library" version="0.3.54" provider-name="OpenAI">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Native Steam games library for Kodi</summary>
        <description>Steam Library. v0.3.54 is rebased on v0.3.53 KPM direct-icons and adds Refresh library for new games.</description>
        <platform>windows</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="plugin.video.mediahub.widget" name="MediaHub Widget" version="0.1.8" provider-name="OpenAI">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Unified Movies, Series, and Steam Games widget paths with AF3/LRS game rating properties, Steam250 aliases, normalized age labels, tagline rows, and no duplicate age row</summary>
        <description>MediaHub Widget. v0.1.8 points all shared rating/game icon paths directly to KPM shared-icons with no local fallback.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="repository.mrgee.kodi" name="MrGee Kodi Repository" version="1.0.2" provider-name="Miftahul Ginda / MrGee">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="MrGee Kodi Repository">
        <dir minversion="20.0.0">
            <info compressed="false">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">MrGee Kodi Repository</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Private Kodi repository for MrGee custom addons.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.artwork.curator" name="Library Artwork Curator" version="0.32.42" provider-name="rmrector + Library Artwork Curator custom fork">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.20.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
        <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.8" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="context_menu.py">
                <label>Library Artwork Curator</label>
                <visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.curator) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,movieset) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,episode) | String.IsEmpty(ListItem.DBTYPE)] + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(MediaType),game) + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(DBTYPE),game) + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(lrs_game),true)</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
        <menu id="kodi.core.manage">
            <item library="context_debug_remove.py">
                <label>AC: remove artwork references</label>
                <visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.curator.debug)</visible>
            </item>
            <item library="context_debug_logitem.py">
                <label>AC: log item debug info</label>
                <visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.curator.debug)</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" start="login" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Remote-only artwork curator for Kodi video libraries.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Library Artwork Curator. v0.32.42 adds dynamic service wait policy for lower idle CPU while preserving scan/job responsiveness.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Remote artwork sources: The Movie Database, fanart.tv, and TheTVDB.</disclaimer>
        <news>v0.32.39 no external TPDb add-on / unified LAC context
- Removed the separate TPDb context add-on from the release package. TPDb is now only an internal Library Artwork Curator feature.
- TPDb poster selection is exposed only from Library Artwork Curator context menu for movies and movie sets.
- Main menu moved Indonesian movie refresh into Maintenance tools.
- Maintenance tools removed TPDb picker/session clear and N/A reset entries.
- Runtime logs/reports now use runtime/* folders while diagnostics ZIP stays in addon_data root and old ZIPs are removed.

v0.32.37 shared auto-scan lock for LRS/LAC
- LAC auto-scan now waits briefly for LRS and participates in the same .kodi-auto-scan.lock file.
- Prevents LRS and LAC progress/final notifications from starting at the same time after Kodi library scan.
- Releases LAC-owned stale locks on service startup and after auto-scan finish/cancel.

v0.32.36 LRS-style auto scan missed-start fallback
- Buffers VideoLibrary.OnUpdate added=true events and consumes them after OnScanFinished when OnScanStarted was missed.
- Keeps snapshot diff when available, and adds a capped cache fallback to avoid false full-library runs.

v0.32.35 LRS-style auto scan pipeline
- Auto scan now follows Library Ratings Scraper's flow: scan-start snapshot, scan-finish pending job, service-loop consume, retry if Kodi DB is not ready, then direct processing.
- Removes the auto path dependency on signal/status/quiet-delay before processing; manual context menu actions remain unchanged.
- Adds duplicate callback guards for Kodi builds that emit both Monitor callbacks and generic notifications.

v0.32.34 Auto scan quiet-delay deadlock fix
- Fixes auto-fill stuck after quiet delay start by avoiding waitForAbort(0), which can block indefinitely on Kodi.

v0.32.33 Auto scan gate fix
- Fix auto-scan queue stuck in signalled state when Kodi leaves Library.IsScanningVideo true after OnScanFinished.
- Skip false full-library auto queue when service receives OnScanFinished without a matching start snapshot.

v0.32.32 Auto scan processing reliability fix
- Added a clear actor-cache-last-run-summary.txt report with found, cacheable, already cached, pending, cached, failed, skipped, and elapsed totals.
- Cache actor thumbnails notifications now use real cache stats instead of always showing 0 errors.
- Runtime performance CSV writes one header only instead of repeating headers for each run.
- artwork-report.txt is now a latest-session report and no longer accumulates repeated version blocks across add-on updates.

v0.32.29 Library Artwork Curator cache skip cleanup
- Cache missing artwork skips non-cacheable Kodi generated video thumbs from .strm and folder paths so they do not keep reappearing as missing.
- Cache progress remains based on actual cacheable artwork work.

v0.32.27 Library Artwork Curator poster fallback and status cleanup
- Auto selection now allows one global poster fallback when no poster meets the configured minimum poster height. Good posters still win first; fallback only prevents sparse/older items from ending with no poster.
- Status/cache summaries now hide internal tvshow season.N.* mirror rows. Direct season artwork remains canonical; mirror rows are compatibility-only.
- Generated video thumb behavior remains one global setting.

v0.32.25 Library Artwork Curator Select artwork provider visibility hotfix
- Select artwork compact filtering now keeps provider visibility: if a provider had candidates before filtering, the top candidates from that provider are kept so TMDb/fanart.tv/TheTVDB do not disappear from the manual picker just because HD or preferred-language filters are active.
- Current-only artwork labels now include the inferred source when possible, for example Current art (TMDb), so existing Kodi artwork is not confused with a fresh provider candidate.
- Select artwork still preserves current/manual artwork and still hides excess low-resolution/other-language candidates when enough better candidates exist.

v0.32.24 Library Artwork Curator context refresh and Select artwork cleanup
- Added context menu action: Refresh all artwork for this item. It refreshes only the focused library item using Refresh All rules while preserving manual/protected artwork.
- Select artwork now uses a compact high-quality candidate list by default: when enough HD/preferred-language candidates exist, low-resolution and other-language candidates are hidden. Current artwork is always kept visible.
- Added Select artwork settings to enable/disable compact filtering, low-resolution hiding, and other-language hiding.
- Reordered Artwork type ON/OFF settings and Select artwork type order to: poster, fanart, clearlogo, clearart, discart, then the remaining types.

v0.32.23 Library Artwork Curator lazy provider and season cache fix
- Auto Fill Missing / Refresh All now uses lazy provider fallback: TMDb first, fanart.tv only for targets still missing strong candidates, and TheTVDB only as final TV fallback.
- Select artwork still fetches provider candidates freely so manual selection is not limited by lazy auto-stop rules.
- Dry run is now hidden behind Advanced > Show expert context diagnostics and caps candidate logging to keep diagnostics usable.
- Context menu entry moved to the root context menu so it can appear on episodes even when Kodi/skin does not expose Manage.
- Season artwork cache now mirrors tvshow season.N rows to direct season rows, keeping direct season as canonical and season.N as compatibility mirror.
- Provider requests now fail faster to avoid long Kodi UI freezes when a fallback provider is slow.

v0.32.21 Library Artwork Curator season fanart cleanup
- Season fanart is intentionally ignored. Seasons now manage poster, banner, landscape, thumb, and keyart only.
- Removed season fanart from direct season targets, dry-run target lists, Select artwork, and fanart.tv seasonal showbackground mapping.
- Keeps 0.32.20 behavior for completeness: one low-resolution fallback for fanart/landscape/thumb when no preferred-resolution candidate exists, and direct season keyart support.

v0.32.20 Library Artwork Curator season provider rebuild fix
- Direct season items now fetch season artwork through the TV-show provider path and map season.N.* candidates back to direct season poster/banner/landscape/thumb/keyart.
- Season dry-run should no longer show provider candidate counts {} only because the mediatype is season.
- Direct season MediaItem now carries its season map so season.N.* provider results can be accepted and applied to the correct season DBID.
- Dry-run logs now include current artwork positions: usable #N, provider #N but not usable, or not in provider candidates. This makes current DB/Kodi art order auditable against Refresh All selection order.

v0.32.17 Library Artwork Curator Select artwork order fix
- Select artwork no longer pins current/selected fanart entries to the top of the candidate dialog.
- Current artwork URLs are now merged into the provider candidate list at their natural provider-sorted position and checked there.
- Current-only URLs that no longer exist in provider candidates are kept at the bottom as fallback/current-only entries.
- Removed the old title-based selected-state guard so provider candidates that match current fanart remain checked correctly.

v0.32.15 Library Artwork Curator OnUpdate/busy hotfix
- VideoLibrary.OnUpdate is no longer used as an auto-fill trigger because Kodi also emits it after playback/resume/watched/bookmark updates for existing items. Auto-fill now relies on ScanStarted/ScanFinished snapshot diff only.
- The Home busy property only counts real processing as busy. A stale/signalled queue no longer shows Stop current process or blocks manual context actions.
- Manual context actions clear a signalled-but-not-processing auto queue before opening Select artwork or Dry run. Real active processing shows a clear warning instead of silently returning.
- Diagnostics export writes to a temporary ZIP, validates it, removes older diagnostics ZIPs, then renames the new ZIP so only the latest export remains in the profile. Profile file lists also hide diagnostics ZIPs.

v0.32.14 Library Artwork Curator context menu/select fix
- Context menu is back under Manage as one entry: Library Artwork Curator. Selecting it opens Add missing artwork, Select artwork, and Dry run artwork selection.
- Select artwork now fetches full provider candidates using the same provider path as dry-run/Refresh all artwork instead of showing only current Kodi art.
- Current art is still shown at the top of each art type and selected by default for multi-art, but provider candidates are also listed.
- Hidden icon/default-video artwork is removed from the Select artwork type list.
- Manual selections are written to artwork-cache.db with MANUAL status so Fill Missing will not replace them.

v0.32.13 Library Artwork Curator context dry-run
- Context menu actions moved to the root context menu and use looser visibility so they appear from library views, widgets, and hub items.
- Context actions now try to resolve a missing DBID from the focused item using DBID first, then uniqueid/title/path fallbacks.
- Added full dry-run artwork selection from the context menu. It fetches providers, selects exactly as Refresh all artwork would, but does not write Kodi art, DB rows, or texture cache.
- Dry-run writes diagnostics/dry-run-artwork-selection.txt and diagnostics/dry-run-artwork-selection-last.txt with full candidate order, usable order, selected URLs, update plan, current artwork, languages, and provider counts.

v0.32.12 Library Artwork Curator quiet auto/cache polish
- Auto Fill waits for a quiet window after Kodi scan/LRS activity before starting, without queued toast spam.
- Auto Fill progress is forced visible for new items and begins after a short cooldown.
- Cache missing artwork now uses stage-only progress: CHECKING TEXTURE CACHE / CACHING ARTWORK / finished toast.
- Removed visible Back items from submenus; keyboard Back/Esc returns to the parent menu.
- Item progress lines no longer include the run phase/action, keeping notifications shorter.
- Diagnostics export checkpoints artwork-cache.db before copying it and closes the menu after notification.
- Updated icon.

v0.32.8 Library Artwork Curator import hotfix
- Fixed malformed XML declaration in addon.xml that made repository import reject the ZIP.
- Keeps addon ID script.artwork.curator to preserve existing userdata and DB path.
- ZIP filename uses the Library Artwork Curator label.

v0.32.4 LRS-style final DB schema
- Uses the new human-readable artwork-cache.db schema.
- No DB fixing/migration/cleanup logic is bundled; install the provided final DB separately.
- Artwork source is now written for new rows: TMDb, fanart.tv, TheTVDB, TPDb, Remote, Existing.
- Episode titles in DB use Series Title - SxxExx.

v0.32.3 LRS-style cleanup hotfix
- Keeps the fixed DB as a separate user-installed file; this add-on update does not bundle a final artwork-cache.db.
- Moves diagnostics/report/runtime files under the diagnostics folder and merges runtime logs.
- Removes Process queued new items from the visible menu; queue remains internal for automatic new-library processing.
- Stops creating processeditems.db for the main LRS-style flow by using artwork-cache.db for legacy processed/set cache.
- Adds Fill missing confirmation dialog.
- Notification format: n/total - TITLE - PHASE ARTWORK - percent.
- Hides dynamic art-type lists from progress notifications.
- Fixes Default (Kodi) language selection so Auto is never sent to TMDb.
- Stops recording art.icon/default Kodi fallback into artwork-cache.db.

v0.32.7 Library Artwork Curator DB-first UI fix
- Renamed visible add-on to Library Artwork Curator.
- Fixed add-on version bump so Kodi reads 0.32.7 correctly.
- Removed duplicate percent text from progress messages. Kodi's progress UI supplies percent separately.
- Hid internal SKIP phase from progress notification; Fill Missing keeps the same clean phase label.
- Moved DB-first skip/apply before expensive provider-ID lookup, preventing TMDb collection search when DB rows are already final.
- Run cancellation now records aborted instead of finished.
- run_items schema no longer uses redundant phase column for fresh DBs; existing DBs remain compatible.

v0.32.2 Library Artwork Curator LRS-style polish hotfix
- New add-on icon.
- Notification format now follows the LRS pattern: {processed}/{total} TITLE - PHASE.
- Cache/prune/clean icon progress notifications include item titles when available.
- Added confirmation before heavy Refresh all artwork.
- Main menu label changed from Scrape missing artwork to Fill missing artwork.
- Settings simplified and artwork type order changed: Poster, Fanart, Extrafanart, Landscape, Banner, Thumb, Clearlogo, Logo, Clearart, Keyart, Discart, Character art.
- Fanart and Extrafanart are now separate global toggles.
- Clean legacy icon skips Kodi default fallback icons.
- Texture cache collection deduplicates URLs and prune includes movie sets while protecting skin/addon/resource URLs.
- Runs now store elapsed_text in addition to elapsed_ms.

v0.32.1 Library Artwork Curator LRS-style hotfix
- Fix artwork-cache.db schema creation for artwork_status and queued_items.
- Add DB self-repair for missing tables and non-fatal DB wrappers.
- Make diagnostics export fail-safe even when the internal DB is broken.
- Fix Export diagnostics ZIP menu handling so it is not wrapped as a processing run.
- Keep queued item DB entries until processing succeeds.
- Clean legacy icon artwork no longer respects media scope; it intentionally scans all video icon slots.
- DB failures no longer stop scrape, clean icon, or diagnostics workflows.

v0.32.0 Library Artwork Curator LRS-style menu/db beta
- Simplify the main menu to LRS-style actions.
- Remove Identify unmatched movie sets from the menu.
- Process queued new items now refreshes enabled artwork for queued DBIDs instead of missing-only.
- Add global artwork-type ON/OFF settings for poster, fanart, keyart, banner, clearlogo, logo, landscape, thumb, clearart, discart, and characterart.
- Scrape missing artwork records N/A status in artwork-cache.db so unavailable slots are skipped next time until Refresh all artwork.
- Move cache operations into Texture cache tools and restrict obsolete prune to known movie/TV/season/episode artwork.
- Clean legacy icon artwork uses a cancellable foreground dialog and ignores library scope, so it can clean all video icon slots intentionally.

v0.31.0 Library Artwork Curator LRS-style core beta
- Add library scope settings: Include movies, movie sets, TV shows, seasons, and episodes.
- Fix automatic new-library processing to use Kodi OnUpdate DBID queue instead of scanning the full library after every scan.
- Normal scans now ignore the legacy Kodi icon art slot completely.
- Add Clean legacy icon artwork maintenance menu for intentional one-time icon cleanup.
- Add artwork-cache.db with run, item, artwork-slot, and maintenance history for easier diagnostics.
- Move Indonesian movie detection to settings with editable folder markers.
- Add actor thumbnail cache setting, default off; actor thumbnails are not mixed into normal artwork scans.

v0.30.18 Library Artwork Curator runtime-debug beta
- Add continuous runtime debug logs for every menu command, service signal, provider request, cache operation, item phase, selection decision, and performance timing.
- Export diagnostics now includes runtime-debug.log, runtime-performance.csv, runtime-items.log, runtime-selection.log, runtime-provider.log, runtime-cache.log, runtime-errors.log, runtime-menu.log, and runtime-service.log.
- Provider request logs redact API keys and sensitive parameters.
- Logs rotate automatically when they grow too large.

v0.30.17 Library Artwork Curator diagnostics beta
- Add Export diagnostics to the main menu.
- Export Kodi logs, filtered Library Artwork Curator log lines, redacted settings, latest reports, Indonesian refresh log, processed-items state, and Indonesian movie artwork snapshot.
- Create a ZIP under userdata/addon_data/script.artwork.curator/ for easy upload and analysis.
- Keep API keys redacted in the settings snapshot.

v0.30.16 Library Artwork Curator movie-only-Indonesian beta
- Limit Indonesian-language specialization to movies inside Indonesian Movies collection folders.
- Remove Indonesian-specific handling for movie sets, TV shows, seasons, and episodes.
- Add explicit details fallback chain: configured/Kodi language, then en-US, then raw details.
- Keep provider/API index order for /images extras and fallback artwork.
- Rename the manual command to Refresh Indonesian movie artwork.

v0.30.15 Library Artwork Curator provider-index-order beta
- Remove rating-based filtering and sorting from automatic artwork selection.
- Keep ratings and likes only as diagnostic information in logs.
- Select artwork deterministically by language priority, provider priority, provider/API index order, and minimum resolution.
- Remove the visible minimum-rating slider because it no longer affects selection.
- Keep localized Indonesian primary-poster handling and TPDb preservation.

v0.30.14 Library Artwork Curator rating-tier-fix beta
- Make all explicitly rated non-poster artwork rank above Not rated artwork.
- Treat the minimum-rating setting as a preferred tier instead of a hard rejection threshold.
- Sort non-poster artwork as: high-rated, low-rated, then unrated fallback.
- Keep poster selection independent from vote ratings.

v0.30.13 Library Artwork Curator unrated-fallback beta
- Treat unrated TMDb, fanart.tv, and TheTVDB artwork as fallback-only candidates instead of assigning a neutral rating of 5.
- Prefer rated non-poster artwork that meets the configured threshold.
- Allow unrated candidates only when no viable rated candidate remains.
- For multi-fanart slots, fill rated candidates first and use unrated rows only for remaining gaps.
- Keep poster selection independent from vote ratings.

v0.30.12 Library Artwork Curator poster-selection-fix beta
- Stop applying minimum vote-rating filtering to posters.
- Select posters by localized language priority, localized-primary promotion, TMDb gallery order, and minimum height.
- Keep minimum rating filtering for non-poster artwork.
- Fix cases where an unrated lower-priority poster incorrectly beat the localized TMDb primary poster.

v0.30.11 Library Artwork Curator dialog-fix beta
- Fix Refresh Indonesian artwork confirmation dialog labels.
- Move the TPDb preservation note into the message body.
- Use short Refresh and Cancel button labels.

v0.30.10 Library Artwork Curator debug-log-fix beta
- Fix Indonesian refresh debug logging on Kodi portable profiles.
- Replace unsupported xbmcvfs append mode with translated local-path append writes.
- Keep the full Indonesian poster diagnostic output unchanged.

v0.30.9 Library Artwork Curator Indonesian-debug beta
- Add a dedicated Indonesian refresh debug log viewer.
- Log scan inclusion, TMDb IDs, current poster URLs, candidate posters, sizes, ratings, localized-primary flags, selected URL, update URL, and JSON-RPC verification.
- Recognize Indonesian Movies (Collection) folder names in addition to [Collection] and plain variants.
- Keep the localized-poster flow unchanged while gathering actionable diagnostics.

v0.30.8 Library Artwork Curator beta
- For Indonesian media, promote localized TMDb details.poster_path from language=id-ID as the main poster.
- Reuse /images metadata for the promoted poster so minimum-height filtering still applies.
- Keep /images gallery order for fallbacks and retain extra-artwork provider logic.
- Preserve TPDb and other manual non-curator URLs during Indonesian refresh.

v0.30.7 Library Artwork Curator beta
- Follow TMDb poster-gallery order within the selected language and provider.
- Stop forcing details-endpoint poster_path ahead of TMDb gallery candidates.
- Use poster_path only as a fallback when TMDb /images has no poster rows.
- Retain minimum poster-height filtering and Indonesian language priority.

v0.30.6 Library Artwork Curator beta
- Enable automatic processing for new library items once after upgrade.
- Add clear log messages when automatic processing is queued.
- Write and read the latest-run report through xbmcvfs for better Kodi profile compatibility.
- Add a configurable minimum poster height and default it to 1000px.
- Prevent TMDb details-endpoint primary posters from bypassing poster quality filtering.

v0.30.5 Library Artwork Curator report-fix beta
- Always write a dedicated latest-run summary when processing finishes.
- Make final notification totals and visible report totals use the same completed-run data.
- Show artwork counts grouped by type and scanned items grouped by media type.
- Keep the rolling history report below the latest summary.

v0.30.4 Library Artwork Curator beta
- Add a new manual menu action: Refresh Indonesian artwork.
- Re-check Indonesian movies, TV shows, episodes, and the Indonesian Movies Collection using language priority id -> en -> no language.
- Preserve existing TPDb and other manually chosen non-curator remote URLs while refreshing curator-managed artwork.
- Keep TV-show season artwork in sync during Indonesian refresh.

v0.30.3 Library Artwork Curator stability beta
- Prevent screensaver and idle shutdown while artwork scans, cache warming, and pruning are running.
- Recover from malformed individual library items and provider-response errors without stopping the full scan.
- Write recovered Python tracebacks clearly to kodi.log.
- Add top-level service exception recovery.

v0.30.2 Library Artwork Curator beta
- Automatically migrate legacy profile data after the add-on ID rename.
- Import old artwork reports, processed-item state, and missing settings such as API keys.
- Rename the internal Home-window busy property to ArtworkCurator.Status.
- Show a clear message when no report exists yet.

v0.30.0 Library Artwork Curator beta
- Renamed the visible add-on from Artwork Beef Video Remote to Library Artwork Curator.
- Added a new Library Artwork Curator icon.
- Simplified settings into General, Artwork, Providers, and Advanced.
- Standard movie, set, TV-show, season, and episode artwork remains enabled automatically.
- Internal add-on ID changed to script.artwork.curator. Uninstall the older custom build with the old ID to avoid duplicate services.

v0.29.8 custom fast beta
- Episode artwork is simplified to thumb and landscape only.
- Legacy episode fanart and fanart# references are removed during the next normal episode scan.
- Movie, set, TV-show, and season fanart behavior is unchanged.

v0.29.7 custom fast beta
- Bulk artwork scans now assign remote URLs without downloading texture-cache files by default.
- Use Cache missing remote artwork separately after the scan when desired.
- Batch texture-cache downloads now use a bounded four-worker pool.
- Texture index is reused for the whole run and the artificial per-item delay is reduced.

v0.29.6 custom beta
- Compact progress actions are now English, title case, and exactly one word: Checking, Reading, Searching, Selecting, Adding, Downloading, Removing, Cleaning, Skipping, Missing, and Done.
- Artwork type remains visible when relevant, for example: Library Artwork Curator: Downloading · fanart3.

v0.29.4 custom beta
- Detailed compact progress stages: checking slots, remote search, library updates, and texture-cache downloads.
- Progress headings include artwork types such as poster, fanart3, clearlogo, and landscape.

v0.29.3 custom beta
- Restore compact persistent Kodi background progress notification.

v0.29.2 custom beta
- Manual artwork scans now use the original compact persistent Kodi background progress notification.
- Cache-missing, prune-cache, and force-recache actions use the same visible background progress style.

v0.29.1 custom beta
- Removed music, music-video, artist, album, and song workflows.
- Remote-only artwork references. No media-folder artwork downloads or extrafanart folders.
- Added TMDb TV-show and season artwork provider.
- Indonesian artwork priority and raster-only filter.
- Added missing-cache, prune-cache, and force-recache menu actions.
- Preserve manually selected extensionless remote artwork URLs, including TPDb-style asset URLs.</news>
        <source>https://github.com/rmrector/script.artwork.curator</source>
        <website>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.curator/</website>
        <license>The MIT License</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets><icon>icon.png</icon></assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.kodi.patch.manager" name="Kodi Patch Manager" version="0.1.74" provider-name="MrGee">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Safe patch manager for Kodi skin and helper add-ons</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Kodi Patch Manager. v0.1.74 adds dynamic service wait policy while keeping pause/OSD monitoring fast and idle states power-saving.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.library.ratings.scraper"
       name="Library Ratings Scraper"
       version="1.5.21"
       provider-name="OpenAI">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="context.py">
                <label>Refresh ratings for this item</label>
                <visible>[String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE,episode)] + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(lrs_game),true) + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(MediaType),game) + !String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(DBTYPE),game)</visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Scrape, cache and publish library ratings, statuses and IMDb Top 250 rank</summary>
        <summary lang="id_ID">Scrape, cache and publish library ratings, statuses and IMDb Top 250 rank</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Library Ratings Scraper. v1.5.21 moves Home/Hub Ends-at into the LRS metadata row, disables native AF3 Ends-at objects to prevent flicker, restores normal polling to 0.10s, and removes the old ready-flag properties.</description>
        <description lang="id_ID">Library Ratings Scraper. v1.5.21 memindahkan Ends-at Home/Hub ke row metadata LRS, mematikan native AF3 Ends-at agar tidak flicker, mengembalikan polling normal ke 0.10 detik, dan menghapus property ready-flag lama.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>