<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="repository.mrgee.kodi"
       name="MrGee Kodi Repository"
       version="1.0.0"
       provider-name="MrGee">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="MrGee Kodi Repository">
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://mrgee-host.github.io/kodi-repository/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">MrGee Kodi Repository</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Repository for MrGee Kodi add-ons.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
<addon id="script.library.ratings.scraper"
       name="Library Ratings Scraper"
       version="1.3.10"
       provider-name="OpenAI">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Scrape, cache and auto-refresh library ratings, episodes and IMDb Top 250 rank</summary>
        <summary lang="id_ID">Scrape, cache, dan refresh otomatis rating seluruh library, episode, serta ranking IMDb Top 250</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Scans Kodi movies, TV shows and individual episodes. Stores normalized and raw rating data from the Kodi library, MDBList, TMDb and OMDb in an independent cache. Stores rating cache independently, refreshes expired items automatically in the background, publishes cached values for Arctic Fuse 3, preloads the next Arctic Mirage slide, and safely updates Kodi movie Top 250 rank through JSON-RPC. Manual full-library scans are handed to the service and shown as a non-blocking background progress notification. Does not write to TMDbHelper private cache. Version 1.3.10 adds missing-only fill: fresh cache rows are skipped when complete, and newly enabled ratings/status are filled without forcing a full refresh.</description>
        <description lang="id_ID">Memindai film, serial, dan setiap episode di library Kodi. Menyimpan data rating terstandardisasi dan data mentah dari library Kodi, MDBList, TMDb, dan OMDb dalam cache terpisah. Menyimpan cache rating secara terpisah, memperbarui item kedaluwarsa secara otomatis di latar belakang, menyajikan cache untuk Arctic Fuse 3, melakukan preload slide Arctic Mirage berikutnya, serta memperbarui ranking Top 250 film melalui JSON-RPC. Pemindaian manual seluruh library diserahkan ke service dan ditampilkan sebagai notifikasi progres latar belakang yang tidak mengunci antarmuka. Tidak menulis ke cache internal TMDbHelper. Versi 1.3.10 menambahkan mode isi yang kosong saja: cache yang sudah lengkap tetap diskip, sementara rating/status yang baru diaktifkan diisi tanpa refresh paksa seluruh library.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
